question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "&quot;Windows NT&quot; is a monolithic kernel.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
     "question": "If you grab the bladed end of a longsword in a specific way, you will not cut yourself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
